[Music]
Jhal
Jhal Kar
Do,
Hello friends, welcome once again to
that point [ __ ] invest, I
am Vishal Chauhan, today we will talk about
accidental insurance of 1 lakh in just ₹2 and
accident insurance of up to 20 lakhs in just ₹40, many people do
not know that there is subscription insurance, if
someone dies in an accident, do
subscribe, if you die, you are watching this, if you
subscribe, then you will get
insurance up to 20 lakhs, it
is very important to see ICICI Lombard because today we
do some job and for just ₹40, we think
that at least we should not do anything to them so that they can get some relief,
what can they do without us, hence definitely obscene and for just
₹40, so please do subscribe to this video, click on the
subscribe button at the bottom,
insurance of both of these for ₹400 means ₹40 per
month, 5 lakh insurance for ₹120
means ₹10 per month and 1  Lakh insurance means
refill the squid for two rupees per month for two months, if you subscribe you
will get subscribe kare
subscribe you pregnancy
like you will subscribe below, if you click on it then your
details will come up last name email ID will come up
only you have to enter date of birth
not normal you have to enter who is the nominee you have to select
and Navami name what is the name of the nominee
if from Banaras then that family parents
member whoever's name and click below and
submit and subscribe then
you will come to know that here life
insurance has two benefits for the graduating
from accidents or cover for
permanent totally subscribe so first of all
half fuel surcharge subscribe
so accident means if you take it from polish then
within twelve months these are some such things will be
on polish you will not get it
after taking it if you were then you would get it
means if you get pregnant of the month
it will come within six months not getting pregnant cover does
not subscribe setting at all means if you
take it today and after 10 minutes there is an accident
then you can get it in it  Waiting
period and subscribe in as a total loss of
21 and function total due to abs cover means
if you have an android and go and
play another one of the quality and get it done then
you will get 20 lakh rupees so as soon as
you click on pay now all the details below, the
option will come, you have to do it
with credit card, you have to do it with debit card,
click on it, as soon as you
click it will be done and
in just two minutes
your policy document will come on your mail on your mail id,
here you go to my money and then
click on accident, inside that also
your name and complete details, all the policy
details will come, so according to me it is very
important, isn't it very necessary,
why are you giving cheap bed on the phone of activation courage, the
question remains that if I am a
judgement, then let it be ₹500 and ₹1000, I will
give 20 lakh 21 thousand but I have
very few clients, it is in lakhs, lakhs and crores
but the mileage is 1 crore, if
people go for 10 lakh then the margin is the same  By reducing it, they
make a group insurance due to which
all the people who take it in this group,
their films, the
best benefit of group insurance is that love comes very less
because most of the people live in it and
what is the
problem with hugging, if there is any problem with group
insurance then if you have any
problem then definitely the claim will be settled for
you, according to that if you
travel to Delhi, you are a big man, you have to go to Delhi
because you go to work, you
travel on this other bike, the bus is ready, then
definitely you should have accidental
insurance, this is the age of technology,
this is the age of technology, you should get
maximum
benefit with less premium, so please keep
one thing in mind, after taking the policy,
do some polish like send mail
or after polishing it, you
can save it by commenting on it and then you
can send mail, take a print out of it,
after taking it out, tell all your family members
that my accident insurance and the
nominee, if you are making the bike to Banaras bank,
making the children, you are convincing
someone, brother, Banaras city  Definitely
tell them and subscribe to your confidence by keeping a copy of it in your cupboard
so that you should
keep all your documents at one place at home as well, all
your documents like Aadhar
card, PAN card, passport certificate,
insurance etc. should be there so that if
God forbid you are in an emergency then
people will know about you or
you should have a subscription for it then your
family members will come to know about it, in this
I have told people that the face photo remains
here and there, so
we did not know that we should
keep those documents, so do not do this at all, so
if you want to take it then install it on your phone,
if not then please loop it,
it is for your and our benefit, we are
getting good insurance value at a low premium, so please
definitely take advantage of it, if you like it then
please like and
share it with everyone who needs it, we will meet soon in the next video, till then
bye khairat